<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">BD Tourist Guider</string>
    <string name="android_n_development">Android \nDevelopment</string>
    <string name="app_description">This is a demo application</string>
    <string name="loader">Loader</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="please_sign_in_to_continue">Please sign in to continue.</string>
    <string name="or">Or</string>
    <string name="login_with_social_accounts">Login With Social Accounts</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="this_is_a_custom_toast">This is a custom Toast</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="popular_tab">Popular Tab</string>

    <string name="pls_chk_internet">Please check your internet connection</string>

    <string name="trending_now">Trending now</string>
    <string name="best_selling_products">Best places</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="this_feature_is_under_development">This feature is under development</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>

    <string name="dhaka">Dhaka</string>
    <string name="chittagong">Chittagong</string>
    <string name="khulna">Khulna</string>
    <string name="rajshahi">Rajshahi</string>
    <string name="barisal">Barisal</string>
    <string name="sylhet">Sylhet</string>
    <string name="rangpur" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">Rangpur</string>
    <string name="mymensingh">Mymensingh</string>
    <string name="chittagong_division">Chittagong Division</string>
    <string name="dhaka_division">Dhaka Division</string>
    <string name="khulna_division">Khulna Division</string>
    <string name="barisal_divsion">Barisal Division</string>
    <string name="rangpur_division">Rangpur Division</string>
    <string name="rajshahi_division">Rajshahi Division</string>
    <string name="sylhet_division">Sylhet Division</string>
    <string name="mymensingh_division">Mymensingh Division</string>
    <string name="cox_s_bazar">Cox\'s Bazar</string>
    <string name="_17_hotels">17 Hotels</string>
    <string name="_5_hours">5 Hours</string>
    <string name="division">Division</string>
    <string name="map_direction">Map Direction</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>

    <string name="cox_bazar_desc">Cox\'s Bazar Beach, located at Cox\'s Bazar, Bangladesh, is the longest natural sea beach in the world running 120 kilometres and 5th longest beach after Praia do Cassino of Brazil, Padre Island on the US Gulf Coast, Eighty Mile Beach in Western Australia, and Ninety Mile Beach of Australia</string>
    <string name="cox_s_bazar_sea_beach">Cox\'s Bazar Sea Beach</string>
    <string name="tour">tour</string>
    <string name="pls_turn_on_internet">Please turn on  internet connection</string>
    <string name="all_time_best_selling_products">All time best visiting places</string>


    <!-- Chandranath Pahar -->
    <string name="place_chandranath_pahar">Chandranath Pahar</string>
    <string name="place_chandranath_pahar_description">Chandranath Pahar is a hill located in Sitakunda, Chittagong, offering breathtaking views and a spiritual atmosphere.</string>

    <!-- Guliakhali Sea Beach -->
    <string name="place_guliakhali_sea_beach">Guliakhali Sea Beach</string>
    <string name="place_guliakhali_sea_beach_description">Guliakhali Sea Beach is a serene coastal area in Bangladesh, providing a tranquil escape and picturesque views.</string>
    <string name="sitakund">Sitakund</string>

    <!-- Saint Martin -->
    <string name="place_saint_martin">Saint Martin</string>
    <string name="place_saint_martin_description">Saint Martin\'s Island is a picturesque coral island located in the Bay of Bengal. It is renowned for its pristine beaches, crystal-clear turquoise waters, and diverse marine life. The island offers opportunities for snorkeling, diving, and exploring vibrant coral reefs. Visitors can relish delicious seafood, witness stunning sunsets, and experience the tranquil island atmosphere. Saint Martin\'s Island is a paradise for nature lovers and a perfect escape from the bustling city life.</string>

    <!-- Patenga Sea Beach -->
    <string name="place_patenga_sea_beach">Patenga Sea Beach</string>
    <string name="place_patenga_sea_beach_description">Patenga Sea Beach is a popular beach destination in Chittagong, Bangladesh. It is known for its long stretch of sandy shores, gentle waves, and scenic beauty. Visitors can enjoy leisurely walks along the beach, indulge in local street food, and capture mesmerizing sunsets. The beach also offers horse riding and boat trips for a fun-filled experience. Patenga Sea Beach is a favorite spot for locals and tourists alike, providing a refreshing coastal retreat.</string>

    <!-- Kaptai Lake -->
    <string name="place_kaptai_lake">Kaptai Lake</string>
    <string name="place_kaptai_lake_description">Kaptai Lake is a man-made reservoir located in the Rangamati Hill District of Bangladesh. It is surrounded by lush green hills and dense forests, creating a scenic and serene environment. The lake offers boat rides, allowing visitors to explore its vast expanse and enjoy the breathtaking views. Kaptai Lake is also home to various indigenous tribal communities, offering a glimpse into their traditional way of life. The combination of natural beauty and cultural richness makes Kaptai Lake a must-visit destination for nature enthusiasts and cultural explorers.</string>

    <!-- Buddha Dhatu Jadi -->
    <string name="place_buddha_dhatu_jadi">Buddha Dhatu Jadi</string>
    <string name="place_buddha_dhatu_jadi_description">Buddha Dhatu Jadi, also known as the Bandarban Golden Temple, is a magnificent Buddhist temple located in Bandarban, Bangladesh. The temple features stunning architecture adorned with intricate designs, colorful decorations, and golden accents. It houses a large golden statue of Lord Buddha, surrounded by beautiful gardens and serene surroundings. Visitors can immerse themselves in the peaceful ambiance, explore the temple complex, and gain insights into Buddhist teachings and practices. Buddha Dhatu Jadi is a spiritual and cultural landmark, offering a serene and enlightening experience.</string>

    <!-- Radiant Fish World -->
    <string name="place_radiant_fish_world">Radiant Fish World</string>
    <string name="place_radiant_fish_world_description">Radiant Fish World is a unique aquatic attraction situated in Dhaka, Bangladesh. It is a paradise for fish enthusiasts and nature lovers alike. The world-class aquarium showcases a wide range of exotic and colorful fish species from around the world. Visitors can marvel at the vibrant underwater world, observe fascinating marine life, and learn about different aquatic ecosystems. Radiant Fish World also offers educational exhibits, interactive displays, and informative presentations. It is a captivating destination that combines entertainment, education, and appreciation for the beauty of marine life.</string>
    <string name="cox_bazar">Cox Bazar</string>
    <string name="teknaf">Teknaf</string>
    <string name="bandarban">Bandarban</string>


    <!-- Place Names -->
    <string name="place_ahsan_manzil">Ahsan Manzil Museum</string>
    <string name="place_lalbagh_fort">Lalbagh Fort</string>
    <string name="place_national_parliament">Bangladesh National Parliament</string>
    <string name="place_sonargaon_museum">Sonargaon Museum</string>
    <string name="place_bangabandhu_safari_park">Bangabandhu Safari Park</string>
    <string name="place_bangabandhu_military_museum">Bangabandhu Military Museum</string>
    <string name="place_taj_mahal_bangladesh">Taj Mahal Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="place_hatir_jheel">Hatir Jheel</string>

    <!-- Place Details -->
    <string name="place_ahsan_manzil_details">Ahsan Manzil Museum is a historical palace located in Dhaka. It showcases the rich cultural heritage of Bangladesh.</string>
    <string name="place_lalbagh_fort_details">Lalbagh Fort is a Mughal fort complex in Dhaka. It is an architectural marvel with beautiful gardens and structures.</string>
    <string name="place_national_parliament_details">The Bangladesh National Parliament is the supreme legislative body of the country. It is an iconic symbol of democracy.</string>
    <string name="place_sonargaon_museum_details">Sonargaon Museum is a historical site in Dhaka. It showcases the rich history and culture of the region.</string>
    <string name="place_bangabandhu_safari_park_details">Bangabandhu Safari Park is a wildlife park in Gazipur. It is home to various species of animals and offers an exciting safari experience.</string>
    <string name="place_bangabandhu_military_museum_details">Bangabandhu Military Museum is a museum dedicated to the armed forces of Bangladesh. It showcases the country\'s military history.</string>
    <string name="place_taj_mahal_bangladesh_details">Taj Mahal Bangladesh is a replica of the iconic Taj Mahal in India. It is a beautiful architectural masterpiece.</string>
    <string name="place_hatir_jheel_details">Hatir Jheel is a popular lake and recreational area in Dhaka. It offers boating and other activities for visitors.</string>
    <string name="tourist_guider">Tourist Guider</string>
    <string name="bangladesh">Bangladesh</string>
    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="maps">Maps</string>

    <!-- Add more strings for other places if needed -->


    <!-- Menu Titles -->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="places_of_interest">Places of Interest</string>
    <string name="nearby_attractions">Nearby Attractions</string>
    <string name="restaurants_cafes">Restaurants &amp; Cafes</string>
    <string name="accommodation">Accommodation</string>
    <string name="transportation">Transportation</string>
    <string name="travel_tips">Travel Tips</string>
    <string name="weather_updates">Weather Updates</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="already_in_home">Already in home</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome Back</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="nearby_hotels">Nearby Hotels</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_the_bangladesh_tourist_guider_app">Welcome to the Bangladesh Tourist Guider App!</string>
    <string name="our_app_aims_to_provide_you_with_a_comprehensive_guide_to_explore_the_rich_cultural_heritage_natural_beauty_and_historical_landmarks_of_bangladesh_whether_you_re_a_local_resident_or_a_visitor_from_abroad_our_app_is_designed_to_enhance_your_travel_experience_and_make_your_journey_through_bangladesh_memorable_discover_the_hidden_gems_of_bangladesh_through_our_carefully_curated_collection_of_destinations_including_stunning_beaches_historical_sites_vibrant_cities_serene_rivers_and_picturesque_landscapes_our_app_offers_detailed_information_about_each_location_including_its_significance_historical_background_cultural_significance_and_must_visit_attractions_navigate_through_our_interactive_maps_and_find_your_way_to_your_desired_destinations_effortlessly_our_user_friendly_interface_ensures_easy_access_to_information_making_it_convenient_for_you_to_plan_your_itinerary_and_explore_the_wonders_of_bangladesh_at_your_own_pace_stay_updated_with_the_latest_news_events_and_festivals_happening_across_the_country_our_app_provides_valuable_insights_into_local_traditions_cuisines_and_customs_allowing_you_to_immerse_yourself_in_the_true_essence_of_bangladesh">Our app aims to provide you with a comprehensive guide to explore the rich cultural heritage, natural beauty, and historical landmarks of Bangladesh. Whether you\'re a local resident or a visitor from abroad, our app is designed to enhance your travel experience and make your journey through Bangladesh memorable. Discover the hidden gems of Bangladesh through our carefully curated collection of destinations, including stunning beaches, historical sites, vibrant cities, serene rivers, and picturesque landscapes. Our app offers detailed information about each location, including its significance, historical background, cultural significance, and must-visit attractions. Navigate through our interactive maps and find your way to your desired destinations effortlessly. Our user-friendly interface ensures easy access to information, making it convenient for you to plan your itinerary and explore the wonders of Bangladesh at your own pace. Stay updated with the latest news, events, and festivals happening across the country. Our app provides valuable insights into local traditions, cuisines, and customs, allowing you to immerse yourself in the true essence of Bangladesh.</string>
    <string name="happy_exploring_n_nthe_bangladesh_tourist_guider_app_team">Happy exploring!\n\nThe Bangladesh Tourist Guider App Team</string>
    <string name="search_on_map">Search On Map</string>
    <string name="location_access_required">Location access required</string>
    <string name="turn_on_location">Please turn on location</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">SOMETHING WENT WRONG</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong_try_again">SOMETHING WENT WRONG PLEASE TRY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong_with_location_try_again">SOMETHING WENT WRONG WITH LOCATION PLEASE TRY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="developed_by_rajia">Developed By Rajia</string>
    <string name="coptyrights">Copyrights reserved to team bd tourist guider 2023</string>
    <string name="rangamati">"Rangamati "</string>
    <string name="nafa_khum_waterfall">Nafa-Khum Waterfall</string>
    <string name="nafa_khum_desc">It is among the largest waterfalls in the country by volume of water falling. The wild hilly Remaikree river suddenly falls down here about 25–30 feet or 7.62-9.144 meters. The word Ngafa (ঙাফা) in native Marma language means Baghair fish/ Dwarf goonch and "Khong" means "Ground</string>
    <string name="sundarbans">Sundarbans</string>
    <string name="sixty_dome_mosque">Sixty Dome Mosque</string>
    <string name="hazrat_khan_jahan_ali_tomb">Hazrat Khan Jahan Ali Tomb</string>
    <string name="khodla_math_temple">Khodla Math Temple</string>
    <string name="mausoleum_of_lalon_shah">Mausoleum of Lalon Shah</string>
    <string name="shilaidaha_rabindra_kuthibari">Shilaidaha Rabindra Kuthibari</string>

    <string name="shundarban_description">Shundarban is a mangrove forest in Bangladesh known for its rich biodiversity. It is home to the Royal Bengal Tiger and offers breathtaking natural beauty.</string>

    <string name="sixty_domed_mosque_description">The Sixty Domed Mosque in Bagerhat, Bangladesh, is a UNESCO World Heritage Site. It is an architectural masterpiece and a symbol of the region\'s rich history and cultural heritage.</string>

    <string name="khan_jahan_ali_description">Khan Jahan Ali\'s Mosque is a historic mosque located in Bagerhat, Bangladesh. It was built in the 15th century and is renowned for its unique architectural design.</string>

    <string name="khondla_math_temple_description">Khondla Math Temple, also known as Kodla Moth, is an ancient Hindu temple located in Rajshahi, Bangladesh. It showcases exquisite terracotta artwork and is a significant religious site.</string>

    <string name="lalon_shah_description">Lalon Shah\'s Mazar is the shrine of the famous mystic poet and philosopher, Lalon Shah. Located in Kushtia, Bangladesh, it attracts devotees and visitors seeking spiritual solace.</string>

    <string name="rabindar_kutibari_description">Rabindra Kuthibari, also known as Shilaidaha Kuthibadi, is a historic mansion in Kushtia, Bangladesh, where Nobel laureate Rabindranath Tagore resided. It serves as a cultural heritage site and a museum.</string>
    <string name="satkhira">Satkhira</string>
    <string name="kushtia">Kushtia</string>


    <!-- Puthia Temple Complex -->
    <string name="place_name_puthia_temple_complex">Puthia Temple Complex</string>
    <string name="place_description_puthia_temple_complex">The Puthia Temple Complex is a collection of Hindu temples located in Puthia, Rajshahi. It is renowned for its stunning architecture and intricate designs.</string>

    <!-- Ruins of the Buddhist Vihara -->
    <string name="place_name_ruins_buddhist_vihara">Ruins of the Buddhist Vihara</string>
    <string name="place_description_ruins_buddhist_vihara">The Ruins of the Buddhist Vihara are ancient remains of a Buddhist monastery. They provide a glimpse into the rich Buddhist heritage of the region.</string>

    <!-- Mohasthan Garh -->
    <string name="place_name_mohasthan_garh">Mohasthan Garh</string>
    <string name="place_description_mohasthan_garh">Mohasthan Garh is an archaeological site in Bogura, known for its historical significance. It is believed to be one of the earliest urban archaeological sites in Bangladesh.</string>

    <!-- Choto Shona Mosque -->
    <string name="place_name_choto_shona_mosque">Choto Shona Mosque</string>
    <string name="place_description_choto_shona_mosque">The Choto Shona Mosque is a small but beautiful mosque located in Bagerhat. It is a UNESCO World Heritage Site and showcases the region\'s rich architectural heritage.</string>
    <string name="bogura">Bogura</string>


    <!-- Baitul Aman Jame Masjid -->
    <string name="place_baitul_aman_jame_masjid">Baitul Aman Jame Masjid</string>
    <string name="description_baitul_aman_jame_masjid">Baitul Aman Jame Masjid is a beautiful mosque located in Guthia, Bangladesh.</string>

    <!-- Kuakata Sea Beach -->
    <string name="place_kuakata_sea_beach">Kuakata Sea Beach</string>
    <string name="description_kuakata_sea_beach">Kuakata Sea Beach is a popular tourist destination known for its scenic beauty and stunning sunset views.</string>

    <!-- Floating Guava Market -->
    <string name="place_floating_guava_market">Floating Guava Market</string>
    <string name="description_floating_guava_market">Floating Guava Market is a unique market located in Bangladesh, where guavas are sold on boats floating in the water.</string>

    <!-- Jakob Tower -->
    <string name="place_jakob_tower">Jakob Tower</string>
    <string name="description_jakob_tower">Jakob Tower is a prominent landmark and observation tower situated in Bangladesh, offering panoramic views of the surrounding area.</string>
    <string name="patuakhali">Patuakhali</string>
    <string name="jhalokathi">Jhalokathi</string>


    <string name="place_title_hazrat_shahjalal_mazar">Hazrat Shahjalal Mazar</string>
    <string name="place_description_hazrat_shahjalal_mazar">Visit the revered Hazrat Shahjalal Mazar in Sylhet, Bangladesh.</string>

    <string name="place_title_sada_pathor">Sada Pathor</string>
    <string name="place_description_sada_pathor">Explore the stunning Sada Pathor in Sylhet, Bangladesh.</string>

    <string name="place_title_jaflong">Jaflong</string>
    <string name="place_description_jaflong">Discover the enchanting beauty of Jaflong in Sylhet, Bangladesh.</string>

    <string name="place_title_lalakhal">Lalakhal</string>
    <string name="place_description_lalakhal">Experience the breathtaking Lalakhal in Sylhet, Bangladesh.</string>

    <string name="place_title_ratargul_swamp_forest">Ratargul Swamp Forest</string>
    <string name="place_description_ratargul_swamp_forest">Immerse yourself in the lush greenery of Ratargul Swamp Forest in Sylhet, Bangladesh.</string>

    <string name="place_title_malnichhera_tea_garden">Malnichhera Tea Garden</string>
    <string name="place_description_malnichhera_tea_garden">Visit the scenic Malnichhera Tea Garden in Sylhet, Bangladesh.</string>

    <string name="place_title_tanguar_haor">Tanguar Haor</string>
    <!-- Tanguar Haor -->
    <string name="place_tanguar_haor_description">Experience the breathtaking beauty of Tanguar Haor, a unique wetland ecosystem and a paradise for nature lovers and birdwatchers. Located in Sunamganj, Bangladesh, Tanguar Haor is famous for its serene water bodies, lush greenery, and diverse wildlife. Explore the tranquil surroundings, take a boat ride through the crystal-clear waters, and witness the vibrant birdlife, including migratory birds during the winter season. Tanguar Haor is not only a natural wonder but also holds cultural significance as a UNESCO Biosphere Reserve. Immerse yourself in the enchanting beauty of Tanguar Haor and discover the harmony between nature and humanity.</string>
    <string name="shunamganj">Shunamganj</string>

    <string name="place_tajhat_palace">Tajhat Palace</string>
    <string name="place_tajhat_palace_description">Tajhat Palace is a historical palace located in Rangpur, Bangladesh. It is known for its impressive architecture and cultural significance, reflecting the rich heritage of the region.</string>

    <string name="place_kantajew_temple">Kantajew Temple</string>
    <string name="place_kantajew_temple_description">Kantajew Temple is a renowned Hindu temple situated in Dinajpur, Bangladesh. It is celebrated for its intricate terracotta artwork and exquisite architecture, making it a significant religious and cultural site.</string>

    <string name="place_shopnopuri_amusement_park">Shopnopuri Artificial Amusement Park</string>
    <string name="place_shopnopuri_amusement_park_description">Shopnopuri Artificial Amusement Park is a popular recreational park located in Dinajpur, Bangladesh. It offers various exciting rides, entertainment facilities, and picturesque surroundings, providing a fun-filled experience for visitors of all ages.</string>

    <string name="title_madhutila_eco_park">Madhutila Eco Park</string>
    <string name="description_madhutila_eco_park">Madhutila Eco Park is a beautiful ecological park located in Bangladesh. It offers stunning natural landscapes, lush greenery, and a variety of flora and fauna. Visitors can enjoy activities such as nature walks, bird watching, and picnics in a serene environment.</string>

    <string name="title_china_matir_pahar">China Matir Pahar</string>
    <string name="description_china_matir_pahar">China Matir Pahar is a scenic hill in Bangladesh known for its unique clay formations. The hill offers breathtaking views of the surrounding landscape and is a popular destination for nature lovers and photography enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="tour_guiid_bd_v1">Bangladesh is without doubt one of Asia’s undiscovered gems, but unfortunately (mostly due to a mixture of political instability and natural disasters), Bangladesh has gathered not the best reputation internationally. Bangladesh has yet to experience much tourism and is mostly un-touristed: a foreign face will excite a lot of attention and interest, almost always of a friendly and kindly nature. “Excuse me mam, your country?” were probably the words I heard spoken most to me on my trip. As an un-touristed destination, Bangladesh is relatively free from the tourist-scams that are common in neighbouring India. On the other hand, Bangladesh also lacks much of the infrastructure of neighbouring India, and travelling around can be hard work. Roads can be unpaved, traffic is dire in some places (mostly Dhaka) – for more see the transport section – and transport conditions are basic at best. English is not widely spoken, which can make independent travel difficult in more rural areas. Bangladesh can also be raw: along with the beautiful landscapes, people and places, expect to see a lot of poverty, and a huge amount of pollution and dirt. Don’t come if you’re not comfortable with dressing conservatively, sitting in crowded transport, and experiencing a variety of conditions. Perhaps the best description of Bangladesh I’ve heard is a “more raw version of India” – but even that comparison falls a long way short of the variety and richness of culture available in Bangladesh, and the positive surprises that this small but bustling country has in store for travellers who make it there.</string>
    <string name="nafa_khum">Nafa Khum</string>
    <string name="the_best_water_fall">The best water fall</string>
    <string name="longest_sea_beach">Longest sea beach</string>
    <string name="best_jheel_in_dhaka">Best jheel in dhaka</string>
    <string name="popular_places">Popular places</string>


</resources>